ZAKARIE YARIS

DATA ENTRY CLERK +44 7920 538866

• DETAILS •

+44 7920 538866 zakariaali350@gmail.com

LINKS

Github page

Twitter

o SKILLS o

Micrsoft office

Python programming

HTML/CSS

PROFILE

A highly-motivated, adaptible and responsible med school gradute now pursuing his dream career in software engineering.

My past academic studies have given me a solid foundation in literature, communication and data management. My experience from my previous work also enabled me to develop strong customer service and teamwork skills. I aim to leverage these skills and further pursue my passion.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Data entry/ Office administrator at Golden Gate Cargo Company, London July 2021 — January 2022

Was responsible for managing the swaths of different company data:

- Compiling, verifying accuracy and sorting information to prepare source data for computer entry
- 2. Reviewing data for deficiencies or errors, correcting any incompatibilities and checking output
- 3. Entering customer and account data from source documents within time limits

Junior doctor at Masaka Regional Referral Hospital, Masaka, Uganda

November 2020 — May 2021

Having worked under rigorous acadmemic demands, i have experience in working under intense and challenging workloads. Some of the activities i used to do include:

- 1. Clerking (documenting history, examination, and plans on the patient's file)
- 2. Chasing reports of dozen patients and evaluating them daily
- 3. Documenting everything in the files or on the online computer system

EDUCATION

Medicine and Surgery, Mogadishu University, Mogadishu, Somalia

September 2015 — October 2020

Graduated top 5 of my almost 100 students class

Biology and Chemistry diploma, Elif Pre-University College, Baidoa, Somalia August 2013 — July 2015

High school diploma, Basha'ir Primary and Secondary school, Baidoa, Somalia

September 2003 — July 2013

Graduated second of my class

■ REFERENCES

Feisal Adan from Golden Gate Cargo Company

goldengatcargouk@gmail.com · +44 7952 983168

Dahir Mohamed Abdi from Masaka Regional Referral Hospital

 $dmcyoung 18@gmail.com \cdot + 256708562187$